Guide to the UE District 11 Records, 1940s-1990s UE.15.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- UE Fighting Fund Receipts (Box 80, Folder 4)
- American Condenser, Check Off, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- American Condenser, General, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Cinch Manufacturing, General, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Cinch Manufacturing, Check Off, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Goodman Manufacturing Co., Check Off, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- GM Laboratories, Check Off, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Goodman Manufacturing Co., General, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Jensen Manufacturing Co. Check Off, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Pioneer Gen-E-Motor, Check Off, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Pioneer Gen-E-Motor, General, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Standard X-Ray, Check Off, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Wm H. Welsh, Check Off, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Wm H. Welsh, Check Off, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 17)
- Social Security Withholding, Unemployment, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Financial Statements, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 19)
- Social Security, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 20)
- Financial Statements, 1949-1951 (Box 80, Folder 21)
- Steward Refund Lists, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 22)
- Per Capita Report, 1949-1951 (Box 80, Folder 23)
- American Condenser, Check Off, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 24)
- American Condenser, General, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 25)
- Cinch, Check Off, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 26)
- Cinch Manufacturing Co. General, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 27)
- Electric Storage, Check Off, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 28)
- Electric Storage Battery, General, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 29)
- GM Lab, Check Off, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Goodman, Check Off, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Jensen, Check Off, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Pioneer, Check Off, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Standard X-Ray, Check Off, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Wm H. Welsh, Check Off, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Wm H. Welsh, General, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Contract, Office Staff and UERMWA (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Christmas Party, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Executive Board, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Local 1150, UE Election, 1951-1952 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Membership Meeting, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Newspaper, UE Local 1150 Outlook (Box 81, Folder 14)
- UE Local 1150 Monthly Outlook (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Stewards Council, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Local, Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Local 1150 Correspondence, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- Local Executive Board, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 19)
- Membership Meetings, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 20)
- Peace (Box 81, Folder 21)
- Stewards, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 22)
- Telegrams, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 23)
- Cinch Manufacturing Co., 1952 Contract (Box 81, Folder 24)
- Cinch, Leaflets, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 25)
- Cinch, General, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 26)
- Cinch Manufacturing Co., 1952 (Box 81, Folder 27)
- Perfection Screw Products Co., File of Stewards' Meetings (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Ampro Corp., 1947 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- General Precision Equipment Corp. (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Armstrong Blum Manufacturing Co., General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- E.A. Baumbach Manufacturing Co., 1947 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Brad Foote Gear Works, General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Brad Foote "Independent" Union (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Brad Foote, Strike, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Brad Foote, 1947-1948 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Chicago Gear Works, General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Chicago Metal Manufacturing Co., General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Clayton Mark and Co., File of Stewards Meetings (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Clayton Mark Company, General January-July, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Clayton Mark and Co., General July-December, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Clayton Mark, Independent Union, Negotiations, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Clayton Mark, Stewards (Box 82, Folder 16)
- Combustion Arbitration, Don Savocchia (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Combustion Engineering Co., General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Cribben and Sexton, General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Danly Machine Specialties, General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 20)
- Danly Machine (Box 82, Folder 21)
- Danly Machine Specialties, Stewards Correspondence and Meetings, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 22)
- Excelsior Tool and Die Works, General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 23)
- Foote Bros. Gear and Machine Corp., Grievances 45th St., 1947 (Box 82, Folder 24)
- Foote Bros. Gear and Machine Corp., General (Box 82, Folder 25)
- Foote Bros. Gear and Machine Corp., Grievances 53rd St., 1947 (Box 82, Folder 26)
- Miehle Printing Press and Manufacturing Co. Independent Union (Box 82, Folder 27)
- Miehle Printing Press and Manufacturing Co., General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 28)
- Foote Bros. Gear and Machine Corp., Stoppage, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 29)
- Gaertner Scientific Corp., General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 30)
- Gaertner Scientific Corp., Grievances, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 31)
- Gear Specialties Co., Contract, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 32)
- Gear Specialties, Inc., General, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 33)
- Gear Specialties, Rates, Descriptions and Job Classifications and Seniority Lists (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Hanson Scale Company, General, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Hubbard Spool Company, General, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Illinois Gear and Machine Co., General, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- The Lockformer Co. (Box 83, Folder 5)
- The Lockformer Co., 1947 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Mercury Manufacturing Company, General Mercury Manufacturing Co., Grievances, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Mercury Manufacturing Co., Strike, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Merkle-Korff Gear Company, General, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Midwestern Tool Company, General, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Miehle Printing Press and Manufacturing Co., Stewards Minutes and Correspondence, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Minneapolis-Honeywell Reg. Co., General, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Minneapolis-Honeywell Reg. Co., Applications for employment, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Onsrud Machine Works, General, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Perfection Screw Products, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- Perfection Screw Products, Stewards Correspondence and meetings, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Scully Jones and Co., General, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Scully Jones Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Ahlberg Bearing Co., Arbitration, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Ahlberg Bearing Co., General, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 20)
- Ahlberg Bearing Co., Correspondence, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Ahlberg Bearing Co., Grievances (Box 83, Folder 22)
- Ampro Corporation, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 23)
- Ampro Corporation, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 24)
- Armstrong-Blum, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 25)
- E.A. Baumbach, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 26)
- E.A. Baumbach, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 27)
- Brad Foote Gear Works, Arbitration, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 28)
- Brad Foote, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 29)
- Brad Foote, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 30)
- Chicago Gear Works, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 31)
- Chicago Gear Works, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 32)
- Chicago Metal, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 33)
- Chicago Metal, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 34)
- Clayton Mark, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 35)
- Combustion Eng., Correspondence, Chicago and East Chicago, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 36)
- Combustion Eng., Grievances, Chicago and East Chicago, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 37)
- Cribben & Sexton, Arbitration, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 38)
- Cribben & Sexton Arbitration, Automatic sprayer PCE Work Rts Dalton stv (Box 83, Folder 39)
- Cribben & Sexton, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 40)
- Danly Machine, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 41)
- Danly Machine, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 42)
- Excelsior Tool, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 43)
- Excelsior Tool, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 44)
- Foote Bros., Arbitration, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 45)
- Foote Bros., Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 46)
- Foote Bros., Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 47)
- Gaertner Scientific, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 48)
- Gaertner Scientific, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 49)
- Gear Spec., Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 50)
- Gear Spec., Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 51)
- Gear Spec., Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 52)
- Hanson Scale, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 53)
- Hanson Scale, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 54)
- Hubbard Spool, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 55)
- Illinois Gear, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 56)
- Illinois Gear, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 57)
- D.O. James, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 58)
- Mercury Manufacturing, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 59)
- Mercury Manufacturing, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 60)
- Mercury Manufacturing, Arbitration, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 61)
- Merkle-Korff, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 62)
- Merkle-Korff, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 63)
- Midwestern Tool, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 64)
- Midwestern Tool, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 65)
- Miehle Press, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 66)
- Miehle Press, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 67)
- Minneapolis-Honeywell, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 68)
- Minneapolis-Honeywell, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 69)
- Onsrud Machine, Arbitration, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 70)
- Onsrud Machine, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 71)
- Onsrud Machine, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 72)
- Perfection Screw, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 73)
- Perfection Screw, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 74)
- Schultz-Jones, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 75)
- Schultz-Jones, Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 76)
- Foote Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 77)
- Foote Stewards and Chief Stewards Meetings, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 78)
- Foote Grievances: A, B, and C Classifications (Box 83, Folder 79)
- Ed Neiztberg - Veteran (Box 83, Folder 80)
- Illinois Gear Stewards and Shop Meetings (Box 83, Folder 81)
- Miehle Printing Press and Manufacturing Co.- File of Stewards Meetings (Box 83, Folder 82)
- Miehle Company Letters (Box 83, Folder 83)
- Mercury Manufacturing Co., File of Stewards Meetings (Box 83, Folder 84)
- Mercury Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 85)
- Miehle Grievances, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 86)
- Ballots & Tally, Election, 2/14/1954 (Box 83, Folder 87)
- Victory (Solidarity, Etc.) (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, Cars, Planes, Ships, Etc. (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Sam Kushner, Rm. 803 166 w. Jackson Blvd. (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Political Action (PEACE C/VR Liberties, Anti-labor, Taxes) (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Action (Strikes, Demands, Grievances, Etc.) (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Unfiled (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Women (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Safety (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Holidays (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Speed up (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Sports and Recreation (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Strikes-Action (Box 84, Folder 12)
- UE Emblem (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Unemployment (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Wage Cuts and Speed Up (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Cartoons (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Drawings for Leaflets (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Meetings (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Peace-War (Box 84, Folder 19)
- People, Costumes, Etc. (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Negotiations and Grievance Procedure (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Political Action (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Profits, Prices, High Cost of Living, Taxes (Box 84, Folder 23)
- Propaganda Press (Box 84, Folder 24)
- Radio and Press (Box 84, Folder 25)
- Red Baiting, Justice, Un-American, McCarthyism (Box 84, Folder 26)
- Union Cards (Box 85)
- Union Cards (Box 86)
- Union Cards (Box 87)
- Union Cards (Box 88)
- Union Cards (Box 89)
- Union Cards (Box 90)
- Union Cards (Box 91)
- Union Cards (Box 92)
- Union Cards (Box 93)
- Union Cards (Box 94)
- Union Cards (Box 95)
- Union Cards (Box 96)
- Union Cards (Box 97)
- United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers-UE (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Constitution- UERMWA (Box 98, Folder 2)
- UE District 11, General (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Milton Burns, International Representative (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Ernest DeMaio (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Mel Krantzler (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Grant Oakes (Box 98, Folder 7)
- UE District 11 Minutes (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Strike Policy Committee (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Benefit Association of Railway Employees, Industrial Division (Box 98, Folder 10)
- UE Building (Box 98, Folder 11)
- UE National Attack on Taft-Hartley NLRB, Compliance (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Contract and Way of UE 1114 Plants (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Elections, Local 1114, 1951-1952 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- UE, Local 1114, Executive Board (Box 98, Folder 15)
- UE Local 1114, General (Box 98, Folder 16)
- Leaflets (Box 98, Folder 17)
- UE-Legislative Questions (Box 98, Folder 18)
- Membership (Box 98, Folder 19)
- Officers Report, 1948 (Box 98, Folder 20)
- UE Local 1114, Chief Stewards and Stewards (Box 98, Folder 21)
- Stewards' Certification, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 22)
- Trustee (Box 98, Folder 23)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics, Department of Labor, Publications and Releases (Box 98, Folder 24)
- American Committee for the Protection of Foreign-Born (Box 98, Folder 25)
- American Arbitration Association, 1949 (Box 98, Folder 26)
- Chicago Council for Labor Unity (Box 98, Folder 27)
- Civil Rights (Box 98, Folder 28)
- Organizers' Bulletin, 1950 (Box 98, Folder 29)
- Congress, National and State (Box 98, Folder 30)
- Consumers Union (Box 98, Folder 31)
- FEPC (Box 98, Folder 32)
- FBI (Box 98, Folder 33)
- Federal Mediation Service (Box 98, Folder 34)
- General Correspondence (Box 98, Folder 35)
- Rothstein and Meyers Attorneys (Box 98, Folder 36)
- Chicago Negro Labor Council (Box 98, Folder 37)
- Newspaper Clippings, Local 1114 (Box 98, Folder 38)
- Political Parties and Activities (Box 98, Folder 39)
- Peace (Box 98, Folder 40)
- Progressive Party (Box 98, Folder 41)
- Smith Act Trial Reports (Box 98, Folder 42)
- Unions other than UE (Box 98, Folder 43)
- Wage and Salary Stabilization Handbook (Box 98, Folder 44)
- W.S.B. Wage Freeze (Box 98, Folder 45)
- Bartley, Valentine (Trial) (Box 98, Folder 46)
- Circular Letters (Box 98, Folder 47)
- Educational and Publicity Material, Releases, Etc. (Box 98, Folder 48)
- Julius Emspak (Box 98, Folder 49)
- UE Pacts for Action (Box 98, Folder 50)
- UE FEPC (Box 98, Folder 51)
- UERMINA- Financial Statements (Box 98, Folder 52)
- Albert Fitzgerald (Box 98, Folder 53)
- Form Letters- Miscellaneous (Box 98, Folder 54)
- UERMWA- General Correspondence (Box 98, Folder 55)
- UE- General Executive Board (Box 98, Folder 56)
- UE Leaflets, Form Letters only, see Literature File (Box 99, Folder 1)
- UE Legislative and Political Action Bulletin (Box 99, Folder 2)
- James Matles (Box 99, Folder 3)
- UE 17th National Convention (Box 99, Folder 4)
- UE Convention Delegates Kit (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Hanson Scale Co., General, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- UE News (Box 99, Folder 7)
- UE Press Release (Box 99, Folder 8)
- UE Radio Scripts and Program Material (Box 99, Folder 9)
- UE Wage Freeze Facts (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Wages- UE Policy Regulations (Box 99, Folder 11)
- UE Washington Office (Box 99, Folder 12)
- UE Locals Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Unemployment Questionnaire 1114 (Box 99, Folder 14)
- Wage and Contract Demands for Local 1114, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 15)
- Wage Data: Surveys, Etc., Local 1114, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 16)
- Clayton Mark, Election Campaign (Taft-Hartley Election), 3-12-48 (Box 99, Folder 17)
- Local Records, 1960-1987 (Box 100)
- E.A. Baumbach MFG. Co. W.L.B. Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Armstrong Blum (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Armstrong Blum, Company's Briefs and Exhibits W.L.B. (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Armstrong Blum, W.L.B. Contracts and Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Armstrong Blum, Hearings, Reports, Recommendations and Directive Orders W.L.B (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Armstrong Blum, W.L.B., Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Ampro Corporation, W.L.B. Correspondence (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Ampro Corporation, W.L.B., Hearings, Reports, Recommendations and Directive Orders (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Danly Machine Specialties, Company's Briefs and Exhibits (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Danly Machine Specialties, W.L.B., Correspondence (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Danly Machine Specialties, W.L.B., Unions Briefs and Exhibits (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Danly Machine Specialties, Hearings, Reports, and Recommendations and Directive Orders (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Danly, NWSB (Box 101, Folder 13)
- Cribben and Sexton, War Labor Board (Union and Co. Exhibits-Decisions), 1945-1946 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Clayton Mark and Co. War Labor Board, 1945 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Chicago Metal Manufacturing Co. W.L.B., Correspondence (Box 101, Folder 16)
- Chicago Metal Manufacturing Co. W.L.B., Union's Briefs and Exhibits (Box 101, Folder 17)
- Chicago Metal Manufacturing Co. W.L.B., Company's Briefs and Exhibits (Box 101, Folder 18)
- Chicago Metal Manufacturing Co. W.L.B., Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 19)
- Danly Machine Specialties W.L.B. Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 20)
- D.O. James W.L.B. Correspondence (Box 101, Folder 21)
- D.O. James W.L.B. Miscellaneous Briefs and Exhibits (Box 101, Folder 22)
- Brad Foote Gear Co., War Labor Board, 1945 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Chicago Metal Manufacturing Co. Hearings, Reports and Recommendations and Directive Orders (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Ahlberg Bearing War Labor Board- Hearings, Recommendations and Directive Orders and Union's and Company's Comments on Recommendation arranged according to date (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Ahlberg Bearing War Labor Board-Company's Briefs and Exhibits, Comments, Petitions for Reconsideration and Review arranged according to date (Box 102, Folder 4)
- E.A. Baumbach Manufacturing Co., W.L.B. Correspondence (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Elli's Dreier Co., National Labor Board (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Illinois Tool Works National Labor Relation Board (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Ampro Corporations Correspondence W.L.B. (Box 102, Folder 8)
- Ampro Corp Union Briefs and Exhibits W.L.B. (Box 102, Folder 9)
- Ampro Corp. W.L.B. Company's Briefs and Exhibits (Box 102, Folder 10)
- Combustion Engineering Co., Inc. W.L.B. (Box 102, Folder 11)
- Bell and Howell Company N.L.R.B. (Box 102, Folder 12)
- American Gear Company N.L.R.B. (Box 102, Folder 13)
- Ahlberg Bearing W.L.B. Union's Briefs and Exhibits, Comments, Petitions for Reconsideration and Review filed according to date (Box 102, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1944-1988 (Box 103)
- Local Records, 1943-1945 (Box 104)
- Foote Bros. Contract, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Foote Bros. Gear and Machine Corp. Negotiations, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Foote Bros. Gear and Machine Corp. (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Foote Bros. National Labor Relations Board (Box 105, Folder 4)
- UE Canada, 40 Years, 1937-1977 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Manual of Practical Political Action (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Dead Jobs- Industrial Gear Division Property of Union (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Definitions, Job Classifications, Industrial Gear Division (Box 105, Folder 8)
- J. Hunter (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Engine Lathe (Box 105, Folder 10)
- Turret Lathe (Box 105, Folder 11)
- Bullard-Colborn Horizontal Lucas (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Thread Milling Worm Milling (Box 105, Folder 13)
- Miles Planner (Box 105, Folder 14)
- Gear Hobber Small Bevel Generators- Large Gear Cutters (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Worm Thread Grinder (Box 105, Folder 16)
- Lo Swing and Multi-cut Lathe (Box 105, Folder 17)
- Gear Tooth Planer Bevel Rougher (Box 105, Folder 18)
- Milling Machine (Box 105, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Jobs Agreement (Box 105, Folder 20)
- All 3rd Step Grievances on Work Definitions (Box 105, Folder 21)
- Occupations and Labor Grades (Box 105, Folder 22)
- 53rd Street 3rd Step Grievances (Box 105, Folder 23)
- Foote Gear Leaflets, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 24)
- Foote Gear and Machine Corp. General, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 25)
- Grievances, 1951 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Danly Machine Spec General, 1951 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Danly "The Reflector", 1951 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Danly Negotiations (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Grievance #B 1303 John Wright (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Danly Strike, June 12 - July 17, 1950 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Danly Machine National Labor Relations Board (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Danly Machine Specialties, Inc. (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Danly Machine Specialties Local 1114 Contracts (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Danly Negotiations, 1945 (Box 106, Folder 10)
- Perfection Screw Negotiations, 1949 (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Perfection N.L.R.B (Box 106, Folder 12)
- Perfection Screw Contract (Box 106, Folder 13)
- Baumbach Negotiations (Box 106, Folder 14)
- Danly Strike, 1950 (Box 106, Folder 15)
- Perfection Screw Machine Products, Inc. (Box 106, Folder 16)
- Perfection Screw Leaflets (Box 106, Folder 17)
- Perfection Screw General, 1951 (Box 106, Folder 18)
- Perfection Screw Local 1114 Contract (Box 106, Folder 19)
- Service Tool N.L.R.B (Box 106, Folder 20)
- Service Tool Negotiations and Contracts, 1950 (Box 106, Folder 21)
- Minneapolis Honeywell Leaflets, 1951 (Box 106, Folder 22)
- Minneapolis Honeywell General, 1951 (Box 106, Folder 23)
- Minneapolis Honeywell Wage Rates (Box 106, Folder 24)
- Shop Stewards (Box 106, Folder 25)
- "K" Miscellaneous (Box 106, Folder 26)
- Minneapolis Honeywell W.S.B. Case (Box 106, Folder 27)
- Chicago Metal Strike Records, 1956 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Ampro Leaflets, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Allied Group Ins. Miscellaneous through December, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Occupations and Labor Grades (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Miehle Printing Press Negotiations, 1952 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Occupation and Labor Grade Book (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Onsrud Machine National Labor Relations Board (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Minneapolis Honeywell Negotiations, 1950 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- Miehle Press Contract, 1948 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- Minneapolis Honeywell General (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Honeywell Negotiations, 1952 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Minneapolis Honeywell General Negotiations (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Minneapolis Honeywell Negotiations, 1949 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- Wage Stabilization Board Minneapolis Honeywell Regulator Co. (Box 107, Folder 14)
- Minneapolis Honeywell Regulator Co. Local 1114 Contracts (Box 107, Folder 15)
- Miehle Negotiations Agreement, 1951 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- Miehle Negations, 1950 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- Perfection Screw (Box 107, Folder 18)
- Time Study (Box 107, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1941-1945 (Box 108)
- Correspondence, 1938-1945 (Box 109)
- Correspondence and Notes, 1943-1954 (Box 110)
- Correspondence and Notes, 1941-1945 (Box 111)
- Correspondence and Notes, 1941-1945 (Box 112)
- Correspondence and Notes, 1941-1945 (Box 113)
- Bulletins, Magazines, and Notes, 1942-1952 (Box 114)
- Miscellaneous Notes, 1941-1946 (Box 115)
- Negotiations and Contracts, 1948-1950 (Box 116)
- Local Records, 1947-1950 (Box 117)
- Pension Brackets, 1946-1951 (Box 118)
- Local Records, 1949-1953 (Box 119)
- Leaflets, 1949 (Box 120)
- Local Records, 1949 (Box 121)
- National and Local Records, 1950-1951 (Box 122)
- Staff Information and Minutes, 1949 (Box 123)
- Local and National Correspondence, 1949 (Box 124)
- Local and National Correspondence, 1949 (Box 125)
- Contract Information, 1949-1950 (Box 126)
- Negotiations and Conracts, 1949-1950 (Box 127)
- Contracts, 1946-1947 (Box 128)
- Local Records, 1946-1948 (Box 129)
- Local Records, 1947-1948 (Box 130)
- Contracts and Negotiations, 1949-1951 (Box 131)
- Correspondence, 1949 (Box 132)
- Leaflets and Election Information, 1947-1950 (Box 133)
- General Notes and Publications, 1950-1951 (Box 134)
- Financial Information and General Notes, 1943-1945 (Box 135)
- Negotiations and Case Information, 1944-1947 (Box 136)
- Local Records and Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 137)
- Legal Information, 1947-1949 (Box 138)
- Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 139)
- L. 1114 40s shops M-W 2 of 3 (Box 140)
- L. 1114 40s shops D-I 1 of 3 (Box 141)
- L. 1114 40s shops Pol. Action 3 of 3 (Box 142)
- Register of Members and Ameritronic (Box 143)
- Coll. pamphlets 40s-50s 1 of 2 (Box 144)
- De Maio-Rosen Subj. Files A-C #1 (Box 145)